lushome.com 2016-01-22

# Lushome | Interior Design and Decor

**Privacy Policy** **Statement No 51411**

We take your security and privacy seriously and we aim to make your experience with us entirely safe and problem free. Please see our security guarantee and privacy policy below.

Every purchase from our site using your credit or debit card number we process using industry-standard PAYPAL secure system. To ensure absolutely minimal risk to you, PAYPAL offers a guarantee for every purchase you make using a credit or debit card.

Our privacy policy covers lushome.com

Organization Name:| lushome  
---|---  
Country:| Canada  
Controller:| lushome  
Web Sites(s):  
| www.lushome.com  
  
 **  
**  
Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access  
**  
**

You can access our Web sites home page and browse our sites without disclosing your personal data.

****The services and links of our Web sites****

Our Web sites enable you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.  
When you do so, other visitors may collect your data.

Our Web sites do not include links to third party Web service providers.

 **  
Automatic Collection of Information**

We automatically log personal data by means such as programming or we link information  
automatically logged by such means with personal data about specific individuals.  
We do so for the following purposes:

  * Technical administration of the Web site
  * Research and development
  * Customer administration
  * Marketing

We use cookies to store personal data or we link information stored in cookies with personal data about specific  
individuals. We do so for the following purposes:

  * Technical administration of the Web site
  * Research and development
  * Customer administration
  * Marketing

 **  
Data Collection and Purpose Specification**

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services.

We may also collect information about you from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations.  
The Data we collect may include primary personal/business information for the purposes of technical administration, research and development, customer administration and marketing.

We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated.

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose.

 **  
Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.

We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by:

  * making reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorised the collection  
of the child’s personal data

We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on  
our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data.  

 **  
Disclosure and Visitor Choice**

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations.

 **  
Confidentiality / Security**

We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method  
to send us their personal data.

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that  
we have under our control from:

  * unauthorised access
  * improper use or disclosure
  * unauthorised modification
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the  
processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of  
our visitors’ personal data.

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities  
except if required by law or other regulation.

 **  
Access to the personal data we may hold about you**

You can ask us, by:

  * sending an email ( )

whether we are keeping personal data about you.

Upon request, which you can indicate by:

  * sending an email ()

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you,

within a month.

– although we may before require proof of your identity.

We will provide the information

at a charge of  
$50  
.

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data:

  * rectified or amended
  * completed

We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data,  
but will give reasons for our refusal.

We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.

 **  
Privacy Compliance**

There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation.

It is also compliant with the following global or regional regulatory, or self-regulatory instrument:

In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the above privacy instrument, we are:

  *  voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedure

Self Assessment procedure

Name or designation of the privacy policy person or service| support  
---|---  
URL| www.lushome.com  
Address|   
Country| Canada  
  
 **Privacy Support**

If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact:

Address :Canada

Email address :| support@lushome.com  
---|---  
URL :| www.lushome.com  
  
We do not recommend another means by which visitors’ concerns may be addressed.

### Disclaimers

This website and its content are provided “as is” and Accord excludes to the fullest extent any warranty or guarantee without limitation. The information or functions of this website are not warranted to be uninterrupted or without error.

Websites and links listed on the Accord website are not controlled by Accord and we are not responsible for any content contained in any such website or company or any loss suffered by you in relation to your use of such websites and links.
